(Penny:)You know, I'm very proud of you
for trying to live with Amy.
- Oh. Thank you.
- Mm.
(Sheldon:)Of course, the ideal way
to conduct this experiment
(Sheldon:)would be with four pairs of
identical Sheldons and Amys.
(Sheldon:)One pair that was neither
dating nor living together.
(Sheldon:)One pair that was dating
but not living together.
(Sheldon:)One pair that was living
together but not dating.
(Sheldon:)And then, of
course, one pair
(Sheldon:)that was living
together and dating.
(Sheldon:)Although, with
that many Sheldons,
(Sheldon:)it'd be such a party,
we'd never get anything done.
(Penny:)That was a cute story.
(Penny:)So, um...
(Penny:)What did you want to ask me?
(Sheldon:)Well, you've lived with your
significant other for some time.
(Sheldon:)I would like this
experiment to go well.
(Sheldon:)Are there any insights
you can share?
(Penny:)Mm. Well, the biggie is,
if she has an insane roommate,
(Penny:)kick him out
as soon as possible.
(Sheldon:)You know, Leonard
and I were very happy
(Sheldon:)before you came along.
(Amy:)You've been roommates
with Sheldon forever.
(Amy:)Do you have any advice?
(Leonard:)I'm trying to think of an answer
(Leonard:)that won't stop you
from doing this.